Stay on the line
02-copper-current/chop/001
line
02-copper-current/chop/002
02-copper-current/chop/003
line
02-copper-current/chop/004
02-copper-current/chop/005
line
02-copper-current/chop/006
02-copper-current/chop/007
line
02-copper-current/chop/008
02-copper-current/lead/001
Stay on the line
02-copper-current/lead/002
Let the current flow
02-copper-current/lead/003
I can hear you
02-copper-current/lead/004
Take it slow
02-copper-current/lead/005
Stay on the line
02-copper-current/lead/006
Let the current flow
02-copper-current/lead/007
I can hear you
02-copper-current/lead/008
Take it slow
02-copper-current/chop/009
line
02-copper-current/chop/010
02-copper-current/chop/011
line
02-copper-current/lead/009
Stay on the line
02-copper-current/lead/010
Let the current flow
02-copper-current/lead/011
I can hear you
02-copper-current/lead/012
Take it slow
02-copper-current/lead/013
Stay on the line
02-copper-current/lead/014
Let the current flow
02-copper-current/lead/015
I can hear you
02-copper-current/lead/016
Take it slow
02-copper-current/chop/012
line
02-copper-current/chop/013
02-copper-current/chop/014
line